A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, New Delhi, India, RG 6, SG 7 FA396
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs, 1955-1973, n.d.; I4; 57 __Boxes __21.4 cubic feet
  Published materials include the annual Progress Reports of the various All India Coordinated Crop Improvement Programs, conference proceedings, special reports, Foundation reports, monographs, periodicals, and offprints.
  The series is arranged in ten subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Maize Subseries 2 - Millet Subseries 3 - Rice Subseries 4 - Seed Development Subseries 5 - Sorghum Subseries 6 - Wheat Subseries 7 - Miscellaneous IAP Staff Projects Subseries 8 - Miscellaneous Food, Crop, and Study Programs Subseries 9 - USAID Projects Under Public Law 480 Subseries 10 - Miscellaneous Reports
  Within subseries, records are arranged alphabetically by subject or type of material and thereunder chronologically.
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Maize, 1957-1972; I4.01
    Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the maize program appears first within this subseries. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
    Correspondence is typically followed by unpublished and published reports summarizing the results of experimental tests. These reports are arranged alphabetically by corporate author. Filed with unpublished reports are manuscript drafts of reports on various aspects of the research programs. Also present are "trip reports" written by staff from the field.
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Corrrespondence - Administration and Organization, 1957-1971 (Box 39, Folder 258)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Corrrespondence - Administration and Organization, 1957-1971 (Box 39, Folder 259)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Corrrespondence - Administration and Organization, 1957-1971 (Box 39, Folder 260)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Corrrespondence - Administration and Organization, 1957-1971 (Box 39, Folder 261)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Corrrespondence - Administration and Organization, 1957-1971 (Box 39, Folder 262)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Corrrespondence - Administration and Organization, 1957-1971 (Box 39, Folder 263)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Full-Time Project Coordination, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 264)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Distribution of Progress Reports, 1959-1966 (Box 39, Folder 265)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Distribution of Progress Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 266)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Distribution of Progress Reports, 1959-1966 (Box 39, Folder 267)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Technical Staff Recruitment, 1957-1960, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 268)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Training Program - Maize Breeding, 1958-1961, 1964-1966 (Box 39, Folder 269)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Workshops, 1957-1961, 1964-1966, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 270)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Workshops, 1957-1961, 1964-1966, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 271)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Correspondence - Workshops, 1957-1961, 1964-1966, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 272)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Interoffice Memoranda, 1958-1965 (Box 40, Folder 273)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Interoffice Memoranda, 1958-1965 (Box 40, Folder 274)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Arbhavi, Mysore, 1957-1968 (Box 40, Folder 275)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Chhindwara, 1957-1969 (Box 40, Folder 276)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Dohad, Gujarat, 1957-1972 (Box 40, Folder 277)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Gangtok, Sikkim, 1961-1971 (Box 40, Folder 278)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Himachal Pradesh, 1961-1965, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 279)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh - General, 1957-1961 (Box 41, Folder 280)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh - General, 1957-1961 (Box 41, Folder 281)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh - General, 1957-1961 (Box 41, Folder 282)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh - General, 1962-1970 (Box 42, Folder 283)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh - Equipment, 1957-1968 (Box 42, Folder 284)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh - Equipment, 1957-1968 (Box 42, Folder 285)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh - Equipment, 1957-1968 (Box 42, Folder 286)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Kalimpong and Kalyani, West Bengal, 1957-1968 (Box 42, Folder 287)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Punjab, 1957-1970 (Box 42, Folder 288)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize experiment stations - Punjab, 1957-1970 (Box 42, Folder 289)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Punjab, 1957-1970 (Box 42, Folder 290)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Pusa, Bihar, 1961-1969 (Box 42, Folder 291)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Pusa, Bihar, 1961-1969 (Box 42, Folder 292)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - General, 1957-1970 (Box 43, Folder 293)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - General, 1957-1970 (Box 43, Folder 294)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 295)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 296)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - General, 1957-1964 (Box 43, Folder 297)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - General, 1957-1964 (Box 43, Folder 298)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 299)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 300)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tarai, Upau, 1957-1967 (Box 43, Folder 301)
    - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tarai, Upau, 1957-1967 (Box 43, Folder 302)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 303)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 304)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 305)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 306)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 307)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 308)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 309)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 310)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 311)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University, Pantnagar, 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 312)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University, Pantnagar, 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 313)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University, Pantnagar, 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 314)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Maize Diseases - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 315)
    - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Scholarships - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 316)
    - Maize International Program - Cambodia, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 317)
    - Maize International Program - Indonesia, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 318)
    - Maize International Program - Malaysia, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 319)
    - Maize International Program - Sri Lanka, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 320)
    - Maize International Program - Thailand, 1961-1966 (Box 45, Folder 321)
    - Maize International Program - Thailand, 1967-1971 (Box 46, Folder 322)
    - Maize International Program - Vietnam, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 323)
    - Reports (Manuscript) - Grant, U. J. and Wellhausen, E. J., "A Study of Corn Breeding and Production in India", 1955 (Box 46, Folder 324)
    - Reports (Manuscript) - Sprague, Ernest W., "Research to Improve Production of Corn in Asia", 1963 (Box 46, Folder 0324a)
    - Reports (Printed) - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Pedigrees of Experimental Hybrids, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 325)
    - Reports (Printed) - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Progress Report, 1969-1970; 2 volumes (Box 46, Folder 326)
    - Reports (Printed) - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Summary Report, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 327)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Agricultural Research Institute (IARI) - Proceedings of the All India Maize Improvement Conference, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 328)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Annual Report, 1964-1966 (Box 46, Folder 329)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 330)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Proceedings of the Maize Conference, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 331)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 332)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 333)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 334)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 335)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 336)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 337)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 338)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 339)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 340)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 341)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 342)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 343)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 344)
    - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 345)
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Millet (All India Coordinated Millet Improvement Program), 1965-1972; I4.02
    Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the millet program appears first within this subseries. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
    Correspondence is typically followed by unpublished and published reports summarizing the results of experimental tests. These reports are arranged alphabetically by title. Filed with unpublished reports are manuscript drafts of reports on various aspects of the research programs. Also present are "trip reports" written by staff from the field.
    - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 346)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 347)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 348)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 349)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 350)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 351)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 352)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 353)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 354)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 355)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 356)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 357)
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Rice (All India Coordinated Rice Improvement Project), 1964-1973; I4.03
    Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the rice program appears first within Subseries 3. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
    Correspondence is typically followed by unpublished and published reports summarizing the results of experimental tests. These reports are arranged alphabetically by title. Filed with unpublished reports are manuscript drafts of reports on various aspects of the research programs. Also present are "trip reports" written by staff from the field. Subseries 3 contains the trip reports of Wayne H. Freeman (1968-1973).
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 358)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 359)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 360)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 361)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 362)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 363)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 364)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 365)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 366)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 367)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 368)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 369)
    - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 370)
    - Correspondence - Cooperative Investigations, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 371)
    - Correspondence - Cooperative Investigations, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 372)
    - Correspondence - Foreign Rice Workers (Visiting), 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 373)
    - Correspondence - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - General, 1967-1973 (Box 56, Folder 374)
    - Correspondence - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - General, 1967-1973 (Box 56, Folder 375)
    - Correspondence - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Draft Agreement with Indian Council of Agricultural Research, 1970-1973 (Box 56, Folder 376)
    - Correspondence - Rice Agronomy, 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 377)
    - Correspondence - Rice Diseases, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 378)
    - Correspondence - Rice Seed Samples, 1965-1971 (Box 56, Folder 379)
    - Correspondence - Treflan (Rice Weedicide), 1970 (Box 57, Folder 380)
    - Project Summaries and Statistics, 1967-1973 (Box 57, Folder 381)
    - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 382)
    - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 383)
    - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 384)
    - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 385)
    - Reports (Manuscript) - IRRI/USAID Quarterly Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 57, Folder 386)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 387)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 388)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 389)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 390)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 391)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 392)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 393)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 394)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 395)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 396)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 397)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 398)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 399)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 400)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 401)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 402)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 403)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 404)
    - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 405)
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Seed Development, 1959-1973, n.d.; I4.04
    Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the seed development program appears first within this subseries. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
    Correspondence is typically followed by unpublished and published reports summarizing the results of experimental tests. These reports are arranged alphabetically by title. Filed with unpublished reports are manuscript drafts of reports on various aspects of the research programs. Also present are "trip reports" written by staff from the field. This subseries has trip reports by Wayne H. Freeman, A. A. Johnson, B. L. Renfro, Ernest W. Sprague, and Jack Dee Traywick.
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 406)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 407)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 408)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 409)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 410)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 411)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 412)
    - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 413)
    - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 414)
    - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 415)
    - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 416)
    - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 417)
    - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 418)
    - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 419)
    - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 420)
    - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 421)
    - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 422)
    - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 423)
    - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 424)
    - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 425)
    - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 426)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 427)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 428)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 429)
    - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 430)
    - Correspondence - Certification and Regulations, 1959-1968 (Box 65, Folder 431)
    - Correspondence - India Crop Improvement and Certified Seed Producers' Association, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 432)
    - Correspondence - Indian Council of Agricultural Research Action Committee on Seed Development, 1959-1961 (Box 65, Folder 433)
    - Correspondence - National Seeds Corporation, No date (Box 65, Folder 434)
    - Correspondence - National Tonnage Club of Farmers, 1965-1968 (Box 65, Folder 435)
    - Correspondence - Training Programs, 1964-1968 (Box 66, Folder 436)